=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
I was told there were no other guests.
قيل لي أنه لا يوجد ضيوف آخرون.
Wait.
انتظر.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Team building.
فريق البناء.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Weiyi.
ويي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
Are you here alone?
هل أنت هنا لوحدك؟
No.
رقم.
My boyfriend is here with me.
صديقي معي هنا.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
He's coming soon.
انه قادم قريبا.
I remember your boyfriend is quite stingy.
أتذكر أن صديقك بخيل جدا.
I guess
اعتقد
it's rare for him to bring you here.
من النادر أن يأتي بك إلى هنا.
Stop being a snob!
توقف عن كونك متعجرف!
My boyfriend is very romantic.
صديقي رومانسي جدا.
Are you hungry?
هل انت جوعان؟
No.
رقم.
I have some meat dishes at my place.
لدي بعض أطباق اللحوم في مكاني.
Do you want some?
هل تريد القليل؟
So well-prepared.
جيد جدا.
They only serve vegan food here.
إنهم يقدمون الطعام النباتي فقط هنا.
Didn't your boyfriend prepare some meat for you
ألم يعد صديقك بعض اللحوم لك
before he brought you here?
قبل أن يأتي بك إلى هنا؟
I'm on diet.
انا في حمية غذائية.
So, no thanks.
لذا ، لا شكرًا.
Let go of me.
ترك لي.
Fine.
بخير.
We have all the things
لدينا كل الأشياء
that you mentioned.
التي ذكرتها.
If you want them now,
إذا كنت تريدهم الآن ،
I can go back to the office and take photos for you right away.
يمكنني العودة إلى المكتب والتقاط الصور لك على الفور.
No worries.
لا تقلق.
Sure. Sure.
بالتأكيد.  بالتأكيد.
Okay.
تمام.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
you lied.
انت كذبت.
Your boyfriend doesn't care about you at all.
صديقك الخاص بك لا يهتم بك على الإطلاق.
I guess he didn't spend
أعتقد أنه لم ينفق
much time planning this trip.
الكثير من الوقت في التخطيط لهذه الرحلة.
It's okay.
حسنا.
It's not troublesome at all.
إنه ليس مزعجًا على الإطلاق.
Look.
نظرة.
Even now,
حتى الان،
what he cares about is still his sales performance.
ما يهتم به لا يزال أداء مبيعاته.
I guess you are nothing
أعتقد أنك لا شيء
in his heart.
في قلبه.
What do you know about us?
ماذا تعرف عنا؟
He is working hard.
إنه يعمل بجد.
He never takes shortcuts.
لا يأخذ الاختصارات أبدا.
You are great at deceiving yourself.
أنت رائع في خداع نفسك.
Don't you think
لا تعتقد
I'm much better than him?
أنا أفضل منه بكثير؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
I think my boyfriend is the one for me.
أعتقد أن صديقي هو الشخص المناسب لي.
And you
وأنت
are a stranger.
غريب.
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
You are shouting.
انت تصرخ.
Do you want everyone to hear us?
هل تريد أن يسمعنا الجميع؟
Everyone must think
يجب على الجميع التفكير
we are doing that stuff publicly.
نحن نقوم بهذه الأشياء علنًا.
Isn't this exciting?
أليس هذا مثيرًا؟
You are shameless!
انت لا تخجل!
Well, I don't mind.
حسنًا ، لا أمانع.
I can show everyone.
يمكنني أن أظهر للجميع.
I don't want to.
لا اريد.
Okay, I got it.
حسنا حصلت عليه.
Fine.
بخير.
Tell the receptionist
أخبر موظف الاستقبال
to turn the lights up in the hallway.
لتضيء الأنوار في الردهة.
And
و
send a set of meat dishes
إرسال مجموعة من أطباق اللحوم
to Miss Sun's room.
إلى غرفة الآنسة صن.
Weiyi.
ويي.
This doesn't add up.
هذا لا يضيف.
Why are your savings
لماذا مدخراتك
so much less this month?
أقل بكثير هذا الشهر؟
Didn't I tell you?
الم اقل لك
I damaged the clothes that I borrowed
أتلفت الملابس التي استعرتها
so I had to compensate them.
لذلك كان علي تعويضهم.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
You didn't save much last month.
لم تدخر الكثير الشهر الماضي.
It's so much less this month.
إنه أقل بكثير هذا الشهر.
At this rate,
بهذا المعدل،
when will we be able
متى سنكون قادرين
to pay for a down payment for our apartment?
لدفع دفعة أولى لشقتنا؟
What's wrong with us renting an apartment now?
ما العيب في تأجيرنا شقة الآن؟
Take it slow.
على مهلك.
Anyhow, I'll save some money.
على أي حال ، سأوفر بعض المال.
Take it slow?
على مهلك؟
Most of my colleagues
معظم زملائي
have already made the down payment for theirs.
قد سددوا بالفعل الدَفعة الأولى لهم.
They can be considered an urbanite now.
يمكن اعتبارهم حضريين الآن.
We are running slow.
نحن نسير ببطء.
By the way,
على فكرة،
you have bought
قمت بشرائها
too many clothes
الكثير من الملابس
and makeup products!
ومنتجات المكياج!
Can't you save a little more on that?
لا يمكنك توفير المزيد من ذلك بقليل؟
Ren Mingyuan.
رن مينجيوان.
I'm a cosmetic sales representative.
أنا مندوب مبيعات مستحضرات التجميل.
It's my job to dress decently.
وظيفتي أن أرتدي ملابس لائقة.
I'm not spending your money.
أنا لا أنفق أموالك.
Why do you care?
لماذا تهتم؟
Do you remember what you said
هل تتذكر ما قلته
while pursuing me?
بينما تلاحقني؟
You said you loved to see me dressing up.
قلت أنك أحببت رؤيتي أرتدي ملابسي.
We've been together for so long.
لقد كنا معًا لفترة طويلة.
I don't care about that anymore.
لم أعد أهتم بذلك بعد الآن.
Save the money that you spend on those things.
وفر المال الذي تنفقه على هذه الأشياء.
Many a little makes a mickle.
كثير قليلا يجعل الدغدغة.
I don't want to.
لا اريد.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Dad.
أب.
Didn't I just give you money?
ألم أعطيك المال فقط؟
Why did you use it up so quickly?
لماذا استخدمته بهذه السرعة؟